

- 7845634550
- dhanapal4550@gmail.com
- www.abrsys.com
- 308, Thiruvalluvar, St, Rajapalayam

SKILLS

- PHP (Laravel Framework)
- NET
- ANDROID
- · MY SQL
- · HTML 5, CSS
- PYTHON (basic)
- MICROSOFT OFFICE

LANGUAGES

- English
- Tamil

CERTIFICATE

• Guvi python Course Certificate

DHANAPAL S

BACKEND LARAVEL DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

I'm a self-motivated professional with 2 years' experience in PHP programming. I kicked off my career as a PHP Developer for the love of languages, logic, and technologies. I'm proficient in PHP and comfortable with few other programming languages and systems. I'm a fast learner, a team player, and strongly believe in accuracy and precision in everything I do.

WORK EXPERIENCE

ABR SYSTEM PRIVATE LIMITED..., Trichy

Jan 2023 - Present

- Digital LogBook (Human Resource Management)
- Timeinlive Service Management Sysytem (laravel)
- · Possessing knowledge and work experience in PHP development tool XAMPP and Workbench. Worked and created project using Laravel Framework

TM INNOVATIONS..., Theni

2021 - 2022

- Worked in Transport Management System with Laravel, developed robust form validations and utilized searching Techniques.
- · Developed Billing/Finance apps using Php and utilized CRUD operations effectively through modules.

ONE BYTE SOFTWARE TECHNOLOGIES..., Rjpm

2019 - 2020

Worked in We++ app developed using android Tool

EDUCATION

Nadar Saraswathi College Of Engineering and Technology, 2015-2019

Bachelor of Engineering (CSE....)